http://www.rakon.com/privacy

synchronising connectivity everywhere
HomeProductsProduct FamiliesSystem SolutionsOCXO and OCSOTCXOVCXO and VCSOXOVCOCrystal FiltersCrystal ResonatorsTechnical ResourcesTechnical DocumentsGlossaryMarketsTelecommunicationsSpace SolutionsDefense SolutionsGlobal PositioningInternet of ThingsOther MarketsInvestorInvestor InfoAnnouncementsReportsPresentationsAnnual MeetingsFinancial CalendarDividendsCheck ShareholdingTop ShareholdersGovernanceGovernance PoliciesConstitutionCorporate Governance ReportBoard of DirectorsGlobal ExecutivesCorporateAboutNewsHistoryLocationsPolicies & ProceduresCertificationsTemexpressRakon IndiaContactContactGlobal CareersInvestor ContactRakon Sales Partners
Home > Privacy
Privacy
Rakon Privacy Policy Statement
In this policy, "we", "our" and "Rakon" refers to Rakon Limited and any of our subsidiaries or affiliate companies as applicable. The purpose of this privacy policy is to inform you of how we collect and use personal information through websites which are owned or operated by Rakon and have an address (or URL) which contains "Rakon"  (the "Websites") or Rakon branded websites which are hosted by a third party (the “Rakon branded Websites”) the “Websites” and the “Rakon branded Websites” together for the purposes of this policy are referred to as the “Rakon Websites”). It also explains how we protect your privacy and what control you have over your information.
The Rakon Websites may include links to other third party websites. These sites are owned and operated independently of Rakon, and may have their own separate privacy and data collection practices. In general, any information you provide to these websites and the Rakon branded Websites will be governed under the terms of their privacy policy, if any.
Rakon has no responsibility or liability whatsoever for the privacy policies of the Rakon branded Websites or any third party independent sites.
By visiting the Rakon Websites and continuing to do so you indicate your consent to the collection and use of personal information in accordance with this privacy policy. We reserve the right to change this privacy policy from time to time by updating it on the website.
Rakon collects information about your interaction with our computer systems which includes but is not limited to:
1.    Use of Rakon’s Websites
2.    E-mail correspondence with Rakon
3.    Connections to Rakon’s internal network and systems
How is your information collected?
You may provide us with personal information such as your name, address, phone number, location, email address and other personal information when requesting or using a service with us, sending us a communication, enquiring about employment opportunities, completing forms or surveys or by completing log-in and password details at any of our Rakon Websites sign-in facilities.
If you subscribe to email notifications from Rakon, you will need to disclose your name and email address, either to us or to a third party service that manages email notifications.
You may choose to disclose personal information when adding a post to a Rakon Website or when commenting on the posts of others. Such information will be viewable by website administrators, certain Rakon staff and, if published, members of the public. Do not post or otherwise transmit personal information of a sensitive nature.
We may automatically collect information about your visit to help us improve the Rakon Websites. This information may include but is not limited to:
o    your IP address;
o    the search terms you used;
o    the pages you accessed on the Rakon Websites and the links you clicked on;
o    the date and time you visited the Rakon Websites;
o    the previous website you visited;
o    your browsing behaviour and the URLs of the pages you visit;
o    your operating system; and
o    the type of browser you use
5. The Rakon Websites may also use a marketing automation system using cookies to track website usage in order to provide customized information related to the specific   interests of the website users. This system enables us to link automatically logged information with specific user information.
6. Rakon may also collect information about you from other available sources, such as public records or bodies.
You agree that Rakon can obtain information about you from, or provide your information to, police or other government agencies information security organisations and other third party organisations.
Rakon can provide information about you where needed to comply with New Zealand or International law or if we believe it will help prevent or resolve fraud, money laundering or other crimes. Rakon can provide your information to third party organisations to prevent or resolve attacks and unauthorised access to our systems. We can provide this information even if you are not involved in such malicious activity.
Rakon is under no obligation to inform you should we provide information about you to a third party. Rakon is not responsible to you or anyone else if we provide information about you for the purposes above.
Rakon recognises you have rights over your personal information. In particular, you have the right to request for more information about what information we collect and process about you, and request a copy of it, to correct your information, and you may have the right to ask us to erase your information in some circumstances. You may contact our Company Secretary via the email:
This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.
We will respond to your privacy requests as soon as we can, and no later than 20 working days from the date of a request. Please understand some requests may require further verification,
This privacy policy was last updated on 22 September 2020
Privacy Compliance
Our privacy policy is compliant with the New Zealand Privacy Act 1993.
This Privacy Statement is subject to change without notice.
About Rakon
Rakon is a global high technology company that designs and manufactures world leading frequency control solutions…
Read More...
Corporate Profile
................................................................................
Available Now!
Rakon NZX Tech Article
Subscribe to Investor News here
Investor Fact Sheet
................................................................................
'Centum Rakon India' is Rakon India
................................................................................
Rakon's involvement with the IoT
................................................................................
Design or Test Engineer? See our latest
Application Notes
..............................................................................
Rakon's FY2020 Review and Annual Report are available here.
.................................................................................
Tweets by @rakonltd
ProductsSystem SolutionsOCXO and OCSOTCXOVCXOXOCrystal FiltersCrystal ResonatorsTechnical ResourcesMicrositesTemexpressMarketsTelecommunicationsSpaceDefensePositioning GNSSInternet of ThingsOther MarketsThe CompanyAbout RakonNewsOur PoliciesInvestorAnnouncementsCustomer ZoneTerms & ConditionsCareersNZ CareersContactContact RakonLocationsInvestor Contactecard
Supplier Zone
© 2012 to 2020 Rakon Limited
PrivacyLegal & CopyrightSitemap
